<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Greg Leo</title>
    <link>https://gregleo-econ.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Greg Leo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 08:46:07 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gregleo-econ.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Castillo, Marco, and Gregory Leo. “Moral Hazard and Reciprocity.” Southern Economic Journal 77, no. 2 (2010): 271-281.</title>
      <link>https://gregleo-econ.github.io/papers/moralhazard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 08:46:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gregleo-econ.github.io/papers/moralhazard/</guid>
      <description>Citation Castillo, Marco, and Gregory Leo. “Moral Hazard and Reciprocity.” Southern Economic Journal 77, no. 2 (2010): 271-281.
Link Moral Hazard and Reciprocity</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Econ 3012 (Int. Micro)</title>
      <link>https://gregleo-econ.github.io/teaching/econ3012/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 21:46:17 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gregleo-econ.github.io/teaching/econ3012/</guid>
      <description>Intro This is the course website for Vanderbilt Economics 3012. This course focuses on the formal analysis of the behavior of individuals and firms and how these behaviors aggregate in a market. We will analyze market performance and determine how performance is influenced by various changes. This page will be continuously updated throughout the semester. Please check it on a regular basis. Consider subscribing to changes using a service such as Visual Ping or Wachete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leo, Greg. “Taking Turns.” Games and Economic Behavior 102, (2017): 525-547.</title>
      <link>https://gregleo-econ.github.io/papers/takingturns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 08:46:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gregleo-econ.github.io/papers/takingturns/</guid>
      <description>Citation Leo, Greg. “Taking Turns.” Games and Economic Behavior 102, (2017): 525-547.
Link Taking Turns</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Econ 8100 (PhD Micro)</title>
      <link>https://gregleo-econ.github.io/teaching/econ8100/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 21:46:17 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gregleo-econ.github.io/teaching/econ8100/</guid>
      <description>Intro This is the course website for Vanderbilt Economics 8100. This is the first course of the PhD microeconomics core sequence. The course will cover the fundamentals of consumer theory, theory of the firm, and simple markets in partial equilibrium. This page will be continuously updated throughout the semester. Please check it on a regular basis. Consider subscribing to changes using a service such as Visual Ping or Wachete.
Textbook(s) Main textbook: *Advanced Microeconomic Theory*, Geoffrey Jehle and Philip Reny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bergstrom, Ted, Rod Garratt, and Greg Leo. “Let Me, or Let George? Motives of Competing Altruists.” Games and Economic Behavior 118, (2019): 269-283.</title>
      <link>https://gregleo-econ.github.io/papers/lmolg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 08:46:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gregleo-econ.github.io/papers/lmolg/</guid>
      <description>Citation Bergstrom, Ted, Rod Garratt, and Greg Leo. “Let Me, or Let George? Motives of Competing Altruists.” Games and Economic Behavior 118, (2019): 269-283.
Link Let Me, or Let George? Motives of Competing Altruists</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Castillo, Macro, Greg Leo, and Ragan Petrie. “Room Composition Effects on Risk Taking by Gender.” Experimental Economics 23, (2020): 895–911.</title>
      <link>https://gregleo-econ.github.io/papers/roomcomposition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 08:46:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gregleo-econ.github.io/papers/roomcomposition/</guid>
      <description>Citation Castillo, Macro, Greg Leo, and Ragan Petrie. “Room Composition Effects on Risk Taking by Gender.” Experimental Economics 23, (2020): 895–911.
Link Room Composition Effects on Risk Taking by Gender</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concavity 1</title>
      <link>https://gregleo-econ.github.io/workouts/concavity-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gregleo-econ.github.io/workouts/concavity-1/</guid>
      <description>Welcome LaTeX formatted equation: \( E = -J \sum_{i=1}^N s_i s_{i+1} \)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My New Webpage</title>
      <link>https://gregleo-econ.github.io/posts/test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gregleo-econ.github.io/posts/test-post/</guid>
      <description>Welcome Welcome to my new website! This website uses the Hugo static site builder. All pages and posts are exported from Org-mode files using ox-hugo. The theme is hugo-theme-console by Marcin Mierzejewski.
Since the page is written entirely in structured org-mode files using markdown, it should be much easier to maintain.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
